I ask the questions
you are my wife
Did you order me to kidnap you?
yes, i did it
Why?
I ordered it to catch you
Who set off the bomb in Changni-dong?
What do you do with that?
You said you never said the same thing twice
Sullivan! Sullivan!
Sullivan, Sulli...
J, James, James Sullivan
Sir, Sullivan...
I also confirmed that the bomb was stolen.
It's dangerous!
Myung-oh...
What is that ice cream?
That guy
gave me ice cream
I was coming home with Doyeon earlier.
Who did you meet?
Sullivan, James Sullivan
you, Mr.
I got the street number wrong.
Who said that?
what?
Am I not dead?
Did I live?
Fish oil, hey, fish oil, fish oil, it hurts
Fish oil, fish oil, fish oil, lived
Oh my, it hurts so much
Oh, I lived, I lived
What is this?
what?
Holy bastard
Where has this guy gone?
what?
Minister Seokjun Kim
Military Supplies Management Act and
Aggravated Punishment Act for Certain Crimes
Arrest for violation
Arrested?
me?
Hey, I have this
This really hurts so bad
I really have to go to the hospital first.
We finally met
Mr. Choi Kang
Was it you who set off the bomb in the neighborhood?
bomb?
In the news
I think it was called butane gas.
Ah
There was also a bus explosion, right?
Seokjun Kim blew it.
You were the one talking through the computer, right?
How did you know about me?
JDD?
Are you laughing?
I'm keeping it alive because I have a question.
Speak straight
The CIA's intelligence and my money
Did this answer your question?
Why did you approach Doyeon?
Looks a lot like Charlotte
Our Charlotte too
I really liked rabbits
Is this all because of Charlotte?
What do you think you would have done?
Because of you
Innocent people died
Then what about my daughter?
What did Charlotte do wrong?
Anyway
Dealing with Seokjun Kim
thank you for your help
Processing?
What are you processing?
Because it's not your business
Don't mind
If you interfere with my work in the future
Then it doesn't end with a warning
Doyeon's father
Hey, hey
Let's have one more drink
Oh no, no, no, no
I ate too much today
Oh, you crazy person, call the assistant manager!
Hey, that bastard
Again, I trust my dad and do things like that.
It's okay!
I'm not drunk at all
Hey, Kwon Woo-sung, you crazy guy.
You really shouldn't drive, huh?
This is Naeunjae
Hello?
by drunk driving
person who commits murder
A person who manipulated the results of a trial
What should we do with these people?
Sullivan?
You have to pay for your sins, right?
now
What are we going to do?
hello?
This human
What are you saying now?
Chairman, this is Naeunjae.
Yeah
Is everything okay?
Nothing much happened, why?
No
Let’s have a meal sometime soon.
Chairman
Woosung got into a car accident.
He's in critical condition now.
What? Woosung?
Chairman
What does this mean?
You have to pay for your sins, right?
Son of the Speaker of the National Assembly
He died last night, in a car accident.
retribution
Hey, still someone died.
He too
You hit someone and killed him.
Daughter of the late famous James Sullivan
He was drunk and driving back then too.
There is a story
Really?
Yeah
discharge day
Put on a shield and say you're on a mission
They just acquitted me and let me go.
Who is discharged from military service?
Are you on a mission? Wow
I don't do it
Bodhisattva Choi doesn’t know that, right?
I came back after not serving in the military.
I know that much, right? uh?
Anyway
Just with my dad’s back
I survived
The original military law is much stricter.
Well, in a chant
In addition to military training...
You know Yeongchang, right?
I'm old, so what?
I know too
It's a piano manufacturing company.
eat
True
If you think about it
I feel sorry for Sullivan too.
So
In Korea, Jojimyeon is a connection.
It's a trial and there's no answer.
I don't want to see that either
Didn’t you hit the lawyer?
I'm eating slowly
Where are you going?
toilet
Oh, I'm eating.
Are you talking about the bathroom?
Did you get anything?
The weapons that Kim Seok-jun smuggled to the Middle East
Sullivan bought it all.
Then that's all
Did you come to Korea?
I don't know the exact quantity
What about Novus?
I met you there last night
I know
The warehouse is empty now
I can't even figure out Sullivan's whereabouts.
What about the people around you?
A few days ago in the hotel lobby
With members of the National Assembly
We were filmed encountering each other.
Ki Yun-si, National Assembly member
Naeunjae
Naeunjae?
Then that person is Sullivan and
What's the connection?
Son of the Speaker of the National Assembly
Helping me get acquitted
Looks like Naeunjae
Kim Seok-jun and Naeun-jae
Giyun City IT Special Zone Site
I bought it in the car’s name.
National Assembly Speaker Kwon Sang-tae
Helped designate IT special zone
It's a personal revenge, after all.
I think the same way
Then next time
It must be better
hello
Did you see the news? Seokjun Kim?
Ah, but where did PD go?
Oh, that's right, that's right, you went somewhere else
Hey, because there is no PD here.
It feels so empty, doesn’t it?
You can see it when the case is over
Boy, I know that
But the guy who set off the bomb
Who are you?
It wasn't in the article?
Well, haven’t you heard anything else?
Yes, we're still investigating.
Maybe
If the Vice Minister tells me
Can you tell me too, sister?
Please
Please tell me, will you let me know?
Ah...
Sujin, have you seen the news?
uh? Hello brother
Mistress
Why does he keep doing that, really?
Promise me quickly
Okay, I'll contact you.
Really? I promised
Oh, why don't you walk away?
Sister, let me know first.
Until I tell you
Don't stop your fingers, sister.
What are you doing?
What is it?
No, the two of you
What did you promise, man?
Uh, news?
uh? tidings?
There is such a thing
Huh? tidings?
Hey, what news do you two have?
We should all know this together, huh?
Fingers, what if I just do it, nigga
Sister, I promised!
Jeonghwan, come to work.
Hey, daughter, did you do well on the midterm exam?
Go home and rest. Why did you come here?
I have something to say to mom
I don't have a mother
Wait a minute
U, D, This, This End?
You speak Korean well
So, is this all?
Uh...
7,800 won
Do you have any points?
Lee Soon-cheol, 1405
Are you Suncheol Lee?
The small intestine and this are the points
Aren’t we writing together?
This isn't supposed to work
I'm just doing it this time.
-Sleep.
- Yes
Yes
With little points
Why are you complaining to the customer?
Daughter, 1,000 points is 1,000 won.
It's all money now
Dad wants to work hard...
Why?
Wow, what a shame.
But where is mom?
Don't look for your mom for a while, okay?
your mom
He is a person who does very big things.
Oh, what can I say, I got over 80 points on the test
Do we have to talk about shoes?
Over 80 points? Really?
really
Where is your cell phone? This doesn't make sense
There's no way I can get over it
Now
Kid, just pick it up and throw it, okay?
So the handle
It rattles and falls out.
Oh, by the way, just give it a few hammer blows.
There's a lot of dirty talk
You are no different
Nagging is the worst thing for me
And next time, to Su-il’s brother.
Please do it, okay?
Wow, I'm just dying of bother, really.
Hey, our Soo-il is an asshole.
Is there anyone you don't know in this neighborhood?
What number of AS is this now?
Uh, Kim Min-seo
80 points?
Is it true?
uh
Uh, no, mom, I'll be there soon.
Uh, okay, okay, okay
Hey, hey, I'm going
If anyone sees
I think 80 points is a perfect score.
Huh?
Ugh!
Women’s President! What's going on?
Ah, ah
Our Kim Min-seo got 80 points in math.
No, no matter what
Hold this knife...
Ah! Oh, this?
Oh, this, that, uh
I fixed the handle.
But is Do-yeon’s dad home from work?
Oh, no, no, that...
I'm going to meet the women's president.
I went to the supermarket and they said I went to the hardware store.
Oh, me?
Do you have any business?
혹시 국회 의원 나은재 잘 아세요?
Uh... we're high school classmates.
Do you know my contact information?
Well, I know.
I called you earlier about Producer Inseop.
They didn’t accept it.
Ignoring the local residents
They say I am not qualified to be a member of the National Assembly.
But why the number?
I have a question.
Uh, what should I give you?
-Where is the piggy bank?
- Piggy bank?
-What will Doyeon use?
- Yes
- Rabbit shape?
Hey there
Hey, that, today that
It's been a while since we gathered together.
let's go together
Is this the night of heroes today?
I'll put you in special
Not today
Oh, why?
Where else should I go alone?
Oh my
As of yesterday, when I left the bunker
He didn't look good
Where have you been?
Meet Seokjun Kim
Anyway, really
Ah, I'm proud of myself, very, huh?
Let's talk a little bit
What if I say it?
Let's go together
What are you going to do together?
brilliant performance
Oh, why?
Hey, you're the only one looking back on flatfish
Well, we
Is this Tsukkidashi? uh?
And there must be Tsukkidashi
The flatfish sashimi shines.
Without even knowing
Now
- I'm leaving.
- That...
Why is it like that?
The residents of Changni-dong are the strongest.
Can we meet?
I think it's your turn now.
They kidnapped a reporter?
Hey, what is kidnapping? It's scary.
just over there
I brought you here because I have something to investigate.
I'm so persistent in digging up bombs right now.
no
What time is it now?
Kidnapping a reporter? Are you sane?
Oh, no kidnapping...
More of a problem
how did you know
A local man came and took it away.
Who is taking it out?
uh
Here it is
Oh, there's nothing special about that record.
Ah, it's suspicious.
I don't think he's an ordinary guy
Choi Kang?
Yes, I am the strongest
Are you alone?
Yes, what about you, congressman?
Me too
What does this text mean?
Seokjun Kim was caught.
Kwon Woo-sung is dead
Isn't it your turn now?
Choi Kang and Sullivan
That we are not part of the same team
How do I believe?
This is the situation to consider now
Probably not, right?
Yes, that's right
I'm being threatened
What kind of threat?
They say they exploded everything.
I guess Sullivan
What do you think you're going to do to the village?
Can I contact Sullivan?
The number you called now is
This number doesn't exist
Oh my, oh my
Please check again...
I definitely got a call from this number.
Rep.
You came alone, right?
That's right
Let's walk a bit
Oh my!
You're a police officer, right? Get here quickly
strength, robbery
Knife, I heard a knife.
This is Lee Geun-cheol
With Sullivan
Please get to know the people around him.
Son of the Speaker of the National Assembly
He died last night, in a car accident.
retribution
If you interfere with my work in the future
Then it doesn't end with a warning
Doyeon's father
They say they exploded everything.
I guess Sullivan
What do you think you're going to do to the village?
- Doyeonah
- Huh?
If you see something strange in the neighborhood
We need to talk right away
Yes, dad
But dad
What's strange?
Ah, a stranger said to Doyeon
It's weird when I say I'll buy you something
The first thing I see
It's strange even if it's in front of my house
Something that existed and then disappeared, something that never existed and then came into existence
It's all strange
Okay?
Okay
Come on, come and go.
Yeah
- Yes
we made before
The branch soil has hardened.
Yes!
Come on, we
I'm going to color it.
blue please
- Yes, what color should I give you?
- It's blue.
Hello, Pinky
Nice to meet you
Wow, so good!
Oh no
As soon as I got home from delivery, it was delivered again.
It's great when business goes well
I make a lot of money
Namyeon will help you get stronger.
Why are you really like this?
Go quickly
- I'll come back.
- Yes
Drive carefully
Are you still roasting sesame seeds?
Looks good
I don’t care whether anyone else roasts sesame seeds or not.
If anyone sees you and me
I know you're very close
Did you hear what Mr. Choi Kang said?
I almost died yesterday
What?
Choi Kang doesn’t talk about it?
Needle Changni-dong Eagle Five Brothers
Isn't it like that?
Ha, where is this?
Do you keep judging people’s livers?
Aren't you talking straight?
Who is attacking?
who attacked
I don't know
Because I hear sirens
He said he just ran away
Ah, yesterday Doyeon’s dad
I also asked for Naeunjae’s number.
didn't you know?
Ah, well, you know what to say
The two of you pretended to be very close, but
Well, I don't know anything
Well, if you're close, you know everything, right?
What did you talk about with Kang and Naeun-jae?
I came here because I wanted to know that.
They said they didn't say much
I have to be able to believe it
Kang, this bastard
What are you doing alone?
Huh? what?
Oh, do you work here?
Ah
Al, 'Ali'
- Researcher?
- Yes
Then you have to study a lot
No?
Wow, that's amazing, huh?
Pakistan, Paki...
No, not long ago
A friend who died in an ATM accident
I'm from Pakistan
I think I did it
Oh my, what should I do, this
I came all the way to a distant country and brought this, tsk
Why are you ordering so much?
Ah, that
Here, uh
Good job, yeah
Cheer up, okay?
What if something happens?
- thank you
- Talking
That's straight
You have to hold it straight and well.
- Good luck!
- Yes
uh
Uh, that's on the investigation side anyway.
It was concluded that there was nothing wrong.
Uh, uh, right
Boy, with that amount.
I just need to finish it
with final amount
- Yes
-Are you busy?
no
I'll go now
I'm going to work outside
I'm busy so let's talk later
You're acting so busy
yes
Vice Minister
You're busy with a meeting.
He told me to deliver the data.
'Through the Kiyun City adoption agency,
‘Adopt to America’?
With Sullivan
Join Us Company Security Team
Rashid dies in ATM accident
The rest of the organization also
I'm looking now
Who is this person?
Noah, born in Korea
I was adopted to the United States when I was two years old.
US Navy Special Forces
From Devilguru
Russian private military company after discharge
He worked in the Ragner Group.
3 years ago to the Sullivan security team
joined
Please check out other members of the organization as well.
yes
Is it your brother Kang’s car?
Should I go see my brother Kang’s face?
I definitely didn't come to see Sujin.
- Brother
- Oh, are you here?
uh? This
Isn't that James Sullivan?
Ah...
Hey, what I said
I need to do you a favor.
yes
- Yonghee.
- Yes
- I'll go first.
- See you later.
- Yes
- Goodbye.
Oh, it's hard
Fish oil, I’m tired.
What's going on?
Oh, hey, what happened?
It's not like it exists.
outside
I came here because my brother Kang had a car.
I didn't come to see Sujin.
Oh, that's right there
It’s not that I don’t want to see Sujin.
No, that...
Oh, what kind of photo was that?
Oh, that's right
Please tell this to Jeonghwan.
It seems like Sullivan was the one who set off the bomb.
James Sullivan?
Sullivan sets off a bomb?
Uh, I guess so.
Sujin told me to tell it to you.
Oh, then you should report it right away.
Now the person
How many people died?
Uh, wait, wait
Not sure yet
Doyeon's father and Naeunjae
Did you meet because of that?
Hey, what did Kang say?
Uh, that
Holding the photo and paper on the desk
He just said he was leaving.
Photo? What picture?
Uh, hey, there's a picture of Sullivan too.
There are other people's photos too.
Oh, what kind of plan are you planning on your own, really?
Myeong-oh
Even though I knew who the person who killed was
There's nothing I can do
My tutoring time is up, so I’ll go.
Let's go together
What's going on and what's going on
Take a look
How can I find out?
Brother
Because I’m close with my brother Kang.
Ask and let me know
If you're curious, ask, man
Uh, are you going?
Eggplant, are you coming then?
Ah, the day before yesterday
I heard you met Myung-oh’s mother?
Did you hear?
With Teacher Park
Are you bragging that you ate Korean beef?
Mother
Can't eat
Oh, that brother is really funny too
When I say let's eat pork belly
He said he didn't like it but
Huh? Do you discriminate against people?
Oh no
Meat discrimination.
I am pork belly
Because Mr. Park is Korean beef
Is that so?
Who sent it?
I'm not sure
Please sign here.
yes
- Goodbye.
- Yes, good work.
Rep.
I feel like I'm not doing anything
I set the time
What time do you set?
Have a live press conference
within twelve hours
at a press conference
Reveal everything you've done
This human
Let's see, let's see...
I can't pass the time
You should not report it to the police
So what are you going to do?
boom
"C4-X Composite Unit Detonation Module"
I should report it to the police
Why are you bringing this to me?
If you report it, it will explode right away.
Did I tell you where the bomb was?
I didn't say anything like that.
Hold on to work
You're making it difficult, Choi Kang.
Are you watching?
Where's the bomb?
I warned you
don't disturb me
Where's the bomb, you crazy bastard?
Because of you
The plan has been pulled
What?
One bomb
It will explode more
Take a good look
now
The number you're calling from doesn't exist.
What should I do?
Did this kid say anything else?
There was nothing else
Hold a press conference within twelve hours.
What press conference?
Minister Kim Seok-jun
Did you look after Kwon Woo-sung or whatever?
Anyway
What those people did
I want to reveal it
Why are you asking the congressman to do that?
I don't know either
It's urgent.
Let’s get together right now.
Come to the dojo
I'll leave now
Yes, Kim Soo-il will go with me too.
Have you received your order for flatfish sashimi?
Why are you looking for Sukidashi?
Hey, hey
They say it's a bomb again, huh?
uh? Hey
Where is this? uh?
Should I step forward?
uh? Where are you?
- gaga...
- Stay still.
I think there are two bombs.
I don't know where it is
Well, he was showing off
I don't know anything
It shouldn't be like this
Quickly start with the bomb
Don't you have to find it?
where is it
You need to know to find it, bro.
In this wide place
It's hard to find in ten hours
So what do you want to do?
What, are we all going to die together?
Why do you keep doing this?
no
Talk to me
For now
people in the neighborhood
How about evacuating it?
All those people?
When all those people move
You know that too, right?
Don't take it out
Don't let it come out the other way
How about doing it?
Evacuate from home?
yes
'Cause I don't know where the bomb is now
Avoid going out as much as possible
Meanwhile we
Let's split up and find the bomb.
I think it's a good idea
be confused
Something else big could happen
Hey, Han, let's give it a try, let's try it
Hey, hey, is it good?
Let's go, let's go, ugh!
Let's go!
Let's go
Then tomorrow morning
Yonghee and Mr. Park
Towards kindergarten and school
yes
And you are the customers who come to the supermarket
Tell me to go home
Yes!
Byeongnam is
Bank manager and the direction of the residential area
Yeah
And Do-yeon's father is with me...
I am
I'll move separately
Because there are places to go
yes
Well then, good luck tomorrow morning.
- Come in, brother.
- Come in.
River, river!
Hey, river
Hey, the strongest
Hey, why are you messing around?
What kind of joke?
Ah, still like that now
In this neighborhood
Exploding a bomb
He said it was Sullivan.
Did you know?
I heard it from Kim Seokjun.
But why didn't you tell me?
He said he also met Naeun-jae yesterday.
Is Naeunjae also involved?
I think so
Not ‘I think so’
It's a thing in our neighborhood.
But why aren't you talking about it?
Sullivan's guys are pros.
I'm no match for you
I'm dying
So it's annoying
Leave all the people in the neighborhood away
Solve it alone?
I’m from the neighborhood too!
But
I'm afraid the locals might be in danger...
What, you have more than ten lives?
a local person alone
Are you going to save everything?
You're sick of that, man!
Okay, what am I saying?
Hey...
Are you leaving already?
uh
Dad, I want water
Uh, water?
Now
here it is
Doyeonah
I'm not going to kindergarten today
No, I can't go.
Why? I have to go to kindergarten
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
Choi Do-yeon
Let's just hang out at home today, okay?
no, no
Today is pinky decoration day.
I'm going
Oh, why in the morning
Are you making your child cry?
Don't go out either.
Why again, what's going on?
- I'll come back and talk to you.
- I hate my dad.
Don't ever leave, okay?
Oh, it's okay, pop.
Uh, Minseo?
Uh, don't go to school.
They told me to stay home
They say, ‘Wow, it’s so sweet.’
Oh, really, yes I have
What kind of college are you going to go to, tsk?
Did you contact the women’s association?
Uh, three houses now.
I didn't answer the phone
I think I should go now
You too, there
To customers coming to the supermarket
Talk to me well and send me back home.
Ugh! uh!
- Home!
- evil!
“Gi-yoon”
These points
There is a lot of floating population
It's a place with a lot of people
It will be different from the explosion of a terrorist group.
Anyway, your message is
A place where it will be delivered well
I guess I'll have to choose...
I selected
The most likely places are like this
Please send this data to me too
yes
But
Can you do it alone?
not alone
Hey, Dongkwan
You take it home and eat it.
- Yes?
- Go home!
hello
Seniors, I bought this.
Eat this until lunch
You must never come out.
I promised, until lunch.
yes
Students, what are you doing?
go back to school quickly
What is it, why is this a fight?
Listen to me man
Oh, what do you say?
Shut up
Write it, you kids, really, Mr.
Oh, what? Mr. Lee
Oh, kids, really.
Hey, mini car
Huh? uncle
These damn kids smoke...
Hey, put it in
Hey, I'm not going to school
What are you doing?
Did you bother this guy?
- Oh, no.
- No?
Hey, great, uh
Listen carefully to what your uncle says.
Go straight to class now
And until lunch
You must never go outside
- Okay?
- why?
- 'why'?
- Yes
Is this kid really calling his mom?
Oh, I get it, I get it.
Hey, let's go
- Uh
- Go, go, go
To the kids in other classes too
Pass it on, uh
- Study hard! uh?
- Don't smoke, don't smoke
Nodam, Nodam, these damn kids are real
Wow, if it were like before...
Hey
You didn't get hit by them, right?
Oh no, brother!
Let's go together
Kindergarten, elementary school
I visited all public health centers and happiness centers.
I visited the senior citizen center and the library.
Oh, it's a real bomb
Is there anything?
Even if there is a bomb, it's a problem
I want to kill you even if you don't exist
This Sullivan bastard
There are three hours left
A house that I still can't contact
have got
I need to go there.
I'll go first
three hours later
Naeunjae was interviewed live on air.
Where?
In the Administrative Welfare Center auditorium
Uh, this is just my opinion.
one of the bombs
Wouldn't it be at the interview site?
Because it's being broadcast live?
-There will be a lot of people.
- Right?
Hey, that makes sense.
Then we spread out and searched for
Shall we meet at the Happiness Center?
Uh, then, then
- Uh
- Yes, I like it.
Bank manager
Uh, where are you going?
Oh, I stopped by the bus stop.
I'm going to the press conference.
uh
Wow, less than an hour left, huh?
You didn't find the bomb, right?
Yes, I'm looking for it...
Wow, Sullivan
This damn son of a bitch, this, Mr.
It's like my hometown
Why are you acting like this?
I don't know if I'm sick or not.
That's right
'Through the Kiyun City adoption agency,
‘Adopt to America’?
Oh, maybe
In this neighborhood
Do you have an older adoption facility?
Adoption facility?
That's what they used to do, but here
Isn’t there only Changri Church?
Did you contact reporters?
yes
To the Changni-dong Happiness Center auditorium
Come by 11:50
Announced
yes
At the hospital
Did you also contact the fire department?
Yes, yes, I put it on hold.
I stopped you from speaking.
don't worry
No, how can you not worry!
This is it
Seokjun Kim
Because of this idiot...
I'm sorry
- Come quickly.
- Yes
no
I've been to almost every den.
There is no
Let’s quickly go to the press conference.
There are 35 minutes left
Ah, the strongest one
Where did you go?
Ah, the river
Hey, I went to Changri Church.
- Changri Church?
- Yes
No sauce, sauce?
What are you talking about?
Are you trying to do it?
'Respected
‘Residents of Giyun City’
Get your mind right, Naeunjae
Anyway
We came this far
Even if it explodes, you won’t lose anything
in front of the whole nation
Become a member of the National Assembly who fights against terrorists
Dear residents,
And you are here together
Dear journalists
Ki Yun-si, National Assembly member
This is Naeunjae
Today I spoke to the Kiyun City bomber.
I came here after receiving threats.
What?
Terrorist threat?
No, this is...
If you do as you say
If you don't do it
After a while
bomb
I said I would blow it up
But I
Never compromise with terrorists
to his threats
I won't give in
Brother, brother
Sullivan's goal
You said I was a member of the National Assembly.
uh
Then the bomb
Where do you think I put it?
Ah, Jeonghwan, I hate bombs.
No, if you're Sullivan
So if I were a terrorist
I'm not hiding the bomb somewhere.
Just use that phone
I feel like it's going to explode
Oh, no way
Ah! Mr.
I heard Sullivan gave me that phone.
Congressman, your cell phone is like a bomb!
what?
Ah...
puppy
Throw it!
Don't come!
rev!
Pastor, hurry!
There's a baby here
Oh my
Oh my, it’s pretty, oh my, it’s pretty
Uh, yeah, yeah
Oh my
No, this pretty guy
Who abandoned it?
uh?
yes
Yeah, yeah, yeah
It's Chunbae
Why is he like this?
Do you know how to smile pretty?
I don't know
Babies
I hear an angel whispering
yes
Amen
What did you pray for?
Although now
Although it is an abandoned entity that no one knows about,
Growing up well
Become someone everyone knows well
boom
Because the congressman is alive
Sullivan isn't done yet.
If you hand it over, Sullivan will tell you
Rep. I will protect you.
It's the anniversary of Charlotte's death in three days.
I think there's something more
Stop looking for bombs
Don't do anything
What on earth do you want?
Is this your revenge?
There is no Doyeon
No matter how much I look, I can't find it
Doyeon is gone
What do you mean!
I will definitely bring Doyeon.
Subtitle: Jang Se-ri